## **Chi Hong Edmund Chan**

### Web Application Developer - <a href="https://edmundchan8.github.io/">https://edmundchan8.github.io/</a>

Kenmore, WA, 98028 USA edd.chan@hotmail.com 206-376-4573

#### **SKILLS**

**Languages:** C#, SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular, Reactjs, Java **Software:** Visual Studios, Visual Code, GitHub, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, GIMP, Brackets

#### **SUMMARY**

Web Application Developer with programming experience. Familiar with creating web applications in C# using Visual Studio and ASP.NET Core as well as designing and creating databases with SQL. Team player who has tackled multiple projects, bringing fellow colleagues together to deliver the best end-product to our service users. Takes pride and ownership of their work and always acquiring programming knowledge to face new challenges ahead.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Intern at Trials and Treatment - OH - Remote Work - November 2020 to Present

Updating client website using Angular

#### Intern at Orca Conservancy – WA – Remote Work - March 2020 to August 2020

- Designed an ASP.NET Core Web Application to store business data
- Project managed and collaborated as a team to deliver the project to our sponsor

# **Member Support Representative** at **Crystalcommerce** - Mountlake Terrace, WA **May 2017 to Present**

- Providing technical support and creating training documentation for our members.
- Working as a team with my colleagues and other departments.
- Documenting, creating and QA of engineering tickets for our engineering team
- Onboarding new members via phone, videos with Zoom and online chat using Intercom.
- Teaching members to layout and set up features of their e-commerce website.
- Organizing and taking on projects to create products for our internal catalog.
- Updated sensitive account details for members.
- Liaising with external partners of our system (TCGPlayer, Amazon, eBay).

#### **EDUCATION**

Associate of Applied Science
Web Application Programming - Programming emphasis
Cascadia Community College - Seattle, WA

#### **UWB Hacks the Internet event 2019 Hackathon**

- Worked in a team of 5 to design a website called Sugar Shield that helped users calculate their blood glucose levels.
- Helped others with HTML and CSS, whilst learning how APIs worked for our website